Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. Competitive Advertisements, Pre-55 Group, 1894-1957
The John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library Duke University Durham, N.C., USA
- Container List
  - Beverages
    - Wines and Liquors
      - National Distillers, 1933-1949, (6 folders)
      - Old Angus, 1938-1952, (8 folders)
      - Old Bushmills, 1936, 1941-1942, (2 folders)
      - Old Charter Bourbon, 1942-1954, (6 folders)
      - Old Crow, 1935-1950, (11 folders)
      - Old Crow, 1951-1954, (4 folders) (Box 54)
      - Old Drum, 1936-1941, (3 folders)
      - Old Fitzgerald, 1943-1954, (8 folders)
      - Old Forester, 1938-1954, (13 folders)
      - Old Grand-Dad, 1936-1951, (12 folders)
      - Old Grand-Dad, 1952-1954, (3 folders) (Box 55)
      - Old Hickory, 1949-1954, (2 folders)
      - Old Overholt, 1934-1954, (12 folders)
      - Old Smuggler, 1947-1954, (4 folders)
      - Old Sunny Brook, 1945-1954, (4 folders)
      - Old Taylor, 1936-1954, (11 folders)
      - Old Thompson, 1945-1954, (9 folders)
      - Park and Tilford, 1939-1941, (2 folders)
      - Park and Tilford, 1942-1954, (12 folders) (Box 56)
      - Pete Hagen's Cocktails, 1943-1946, (3 folders)
      - Peter Dawson, 1941-1952, (3 folders)
      - Pilgrim Rum, 1944-1947, (3 folders)
      - Puerto Rican Rum, 1949-1950, (2 folders)
      - Rums of Puerto Rico, 1952-1954, (2 folders)
      - Remy Martin, 1946-1951
      - Riondo Rum, 1941-1952, (4 folders)
      - Ronrico Rum, 1944-1952, (3 folders)
      - Seagram's, 1934-1941, (8 folders) (Box 57)
      - Seagram's Gin, 1945-1954, (7 folders)
      - Siboney Rum, 1936-1947, (3 folders)
      - Smirnoff, 1934-1954, (3 folders)
      - SoCo (Southern Comfort), 1941-1954, (4 folders)
      - Teacher's, 1946-1954, (4 folders)
      - Three Feathers, 1934-1950, (17 folders) (Box 58)
      - Vat 69, 1934-1948, (15 folders)
      - Vat 69, 1949-1954, (6 folders) (Box 59)
      - J. Wile, 1941
      - White Horse, 1933-1953, (19 folders)
      - Wilson, 1937-1953, (10 folders)
    - Beer and non-alcoholic beer, 1917-1927, (2 folders) (Box 60)
    - Brandy and cognac
      - Miscellaneous, 19363-1954, (11 folders)
      - Arrow, 1941-1943
      - Christian Brothers, 1941
      - Croix Royale, 1945
      - DuBouchet, 1953-1954
      - Fendador (Pedro Domecq), 1941
      - Hiblick, 1941
      - Ron Rey, 1944-1946
    - Cocktails and mixers
      - Miscellaneous, 1936-1946
      - Eggnog miscellaneous, 1947
      - Crosse and Blackwell, 1950
      - Overbrooks Eggnog, 1942-1954
    - Cordials and Liqueurs
      - Miscellaneous, 1936-1954, (13 folders)
      - Amer Picon, 1936
      - Arrow, 1947-1949
      - Bardinet, 1942
      - Croix Royale, 1945
      - Cointreau, 1945-1954
      - DuBouchet, 1953-1954
      - Plantation, 1946
      - Red House, 1944-1945
      - Swanee Pride/Old Melody, 1944-1946
      - Southland Nectar/Cocktail Hour, 1945-1946
    - Gin
      - Miscellaneous, 1936-1947, (6 folders)
      - Miscellaneous, 1948-1950 (Box 61)
      - Barclay's, 1945-1947
      - Cummins Collins, 1945-1946
      - Gladstone, 1943-1947
      - Gold Medal, 1945-1946
      - Graves, 1945-1947
      - House of Kasser, 1945-1946
      - Lloyd's, 1945-1946
    - Rum
      - Miscellaneous, 1936-1952, (7 folders)
      - Caldwell's, 1944-1946
      - Carioca, 1942-1947
      - Daiquiri, 1941
      - El Padre, 1944-1945
      - Havana Club, 1944-1945
      - Jamaica, 1952
      - Marimba, 1944-1945
      - Marin, 1944
      - Old Medford, 1944-1946
      - Old St. Croix, 1944-1945
      - Pedro's, 1944-1946
      - Port Royal, 1943-1945
      - Rhum Negrita, 1936-1938
    - Whiskey
      - Miscellaneous, 1934-1954, (14 folders)
      - Liquor stores, 1934
      - Department stores, 1934
      - Bond & Lillard, 1945-1946 (Box 62)
      - Bourbon de Luxe, 1954
      - Calvert, 1936, 1953-1954, (2 folders)
      - Canadian Club, 1954
      - Century Club, 1943
      - Charter Oak, 1951
      - Chivas Regal, 1952-1954
      - Cobb's Creek, 1936-1937
      - County Fair, 1950
      - Cream of Kentucky, 1948-1949
      - Dominion 10, 1953-1954
      - Fine Arts, 1941-1945
      - Gibson's, 1936-1938
      - G&W 5 Star, 1942-1943
      - Grand MacNish, 1941
      - Green River, 1941
      - Guckenheimer, 1951
      - Hudson's Bay, 1951-1954
      - Highland Queen, 1947-1948
      - Jack Daniel's, 1952-1954
      - Kentucky Tavern, 1954
      - Kessler's, 1943
      - King, 1943-1945
      - King's Ransom, 1936-1942
      - King William IV, 1936-1943
      - Lansdowne Reserve, 1943-1946
      - MacNaughton's, 1951-1954
      - Medley Brothers, 1951-1952
      - Old American, 1936
      - Old Colony, 1934
      - Old Dutch, 1934
      - Old Hermitage, 1945-1947
      - Old Mr. Boston, 1940-1943
      - Old Poindexter, 1945-1946
      - Old Quaker, 1949-1950
      - PM, 1940-1954
      - Pebbleford, 1947-1948
      - Philadelphia, 1941
      - Roamer, 1945-1946
      - Schenley, 1954
      - Town Tavern, 1935
      - William Penn, 1942-1943
    - Vodka, 1946-1954
    - Wine, Bitters, Sherry, etc.
      - Angostura bitters, 1933-1950, (10 folders)
      - Cresta Blanca, 1950-1952, (3 folders)
      - DuBonnet, 1945-1953 (Box 63)
      - G&D, 1941-1942, (2 folders)
      - Gold Seal wines, 1946-1953, (2 folders)
      - Italian Swiss Colony, 1946-1950, (4 folders)
      - Mouquin, 1933
      - Mumm's, 1934-1935
      - N.Y. State Widmer's, 1944-1953, (2 folders)
      - Roma wines, 1944-1953, (9 folders)
      - Sandeman, 1938
      - Valiant, 1944-1950, (6 folders)
      - Wine miscellaneous, 1943-1947, (4 folders)
      - Wine miscellaneous, 1947-1954, (8 folders) (Box 64)
      - Sherry and vermouth, 1943-1954, (4 folders)
      - Vermouth and bitters, 1946-1950
      - Wine/sherry/champagne, 1934-1941, (2 folders)
      - Fruit industry, 1935-1937
      - Liqueur miscellaneous, 1942
      - Liqueur miscellaneous, 1934 (Box 65)
      - McKesson & Robbins, 1935
      - Moet & Chandon, 1934-1935
      - Miscellaneous, 1935-1937, (3 folders)
  - Store Advertising
    - Department stores, 1951-1954, (3 folders) (Box 66)
    - Grocery stores, 1950-1953, (2 folders)
    - Electrical appliance stores, 1948
    - Specialty stores
      - Saks Fifth Avenue, 1943-1953, (10 folders)
      - Best & Co., 1947-1953, (5 folders)
      - Miscellaneous, 1954
  - Drug Products
    - Cold remedies, 1914-1933 (Box 67)
    - Cough drops, 1919-1948
    - Cough remedy miscellaneous, 1929-1954
    - Soap
      - Jap Rose, 1921-1928
      - Lifebuoy, 1938-1953
    - Antiseptics
      - Listerine, 1945-1954
      - Lysol, 1945-1946
      - Procter & Gamble, 1944
    - Analgesics
      - Bayer aspirin, 1945-1954
      - Ben-Gay, 1945-1953
      - Topical treatments, 1938-1954
    - Laxatives
      - Phillips Milk of Magnesia, 1930-1934
      - Sal Hepatica, 1926-1950
      - Petrolatum, 1930-1934
      - Squibb corporate, 1930-1942
      - Laxative/antacid miscellaneous, 1922-1946
    - Dentrifices and toothpaste
      - Pebeco, 1917-1921 (Box 68)
      - Pepsodent, 1926-1939
      - Pyorrhocide, 1918-1929
      - Tooth miscellaneous, 1925-1943
      - Denture adhesives, 1941-1950
      - Squibb Dental Cream, 1923-1935, (5 folders)
  - Tobacco--Cigarettes
    - Camel, 1926-1932, (5 folders) (Box 69)
    - Fatima, 1927-1930
  - Drug Products
    - Dentrifices and toothpaste
      - Ipana (Box 70)
    - Foot Aids
      - Allen's, 1929-1953, (13 folders)
      - B. Nelson, Blue Jay, 1925-1953, (20 folders)
      - Blue Jay, 1922-1924 (Box 71)
      - Callous-Ease, 1932
      - Cal-O-Cide, 1928-1931
      - Coolene, 1925-1932, (3 folders)
      - Cro-Pax, 1941
      - Freezone, 1928-1939, (9 folders)
      - Johnson's Foot Soap, 1941-1943, (12 folders)
      - Ice Mint, 1915-1953, (11 folders)
      - Gets-It, 1922-1931, (4 folders)
      - Johnson & Johnson, 1934-1937
      - Jung's Arch Brace, 1916-1933, (4 folders)
      - Kohler, 1930-1934, (2 folders)
      - Lock's, 1942
      - Phytosin, 1930
      - Scholl, 1945-1953, (9 folders)
      - Squibb, 1922-1924
    - Pharmaceutical houses
      - Squibb, 1942-1952, (7 folders) (Box 72)
      - Upjohn, 1947-1953, (6 folders)
      - Wyeth, 1945-1953, (9 folders)
      - Miscellaneous, 1943-1954, (7 folders)
      - Institutional, 1940-1942, (2 folders)
    - Hemorrhoids and colon health, 1944-1947, (4 folders)
    - Pyorrhea, 1952
    - Rheumatism and arthritis, 1930-1953, (13 folders)
    - Stimulants (No Doz, etc.), 1943-1953, (11 folders)
    - Stomach relievers
      - Bell Ans, 1939-1953, (13 folders)
      - Bell Ans, 1930-1938, (4 folders) (Box 73)
      - Bi-So-Dol, 1933-1953, (12 folders)
      - Brisochi, 1928-1953, (10 folders)
      - Choos, 1947-1953, (8 folders)
      - Intesta-Femin, 1915
      - Jests, 1940-1953, (14 folders)
      - Mother Sill's Seasick Remedy, 1929-1953, (12 folders)
      - Pepto-Bismol, 1942-1953, (10 folders)
      - Phillips Milk of Magnesia, 1949-1953, (4 folders)
      - Phillips Milk of Magnesia, 1944-1950, (6 folders) (Box 74)
      - Tums, 1947-1953, (6 folders)
      - Udga Tablets, 1942-1953, (12 folders)
      - Von's Tablets, 1942-1953, (12 folders)
      - Pape's, 1928-1937
      - Dr. Tripp's Liquor Rheumatica, 1927
      - Nurito, 1934-1941, (2 folders)
      - Acidine, 1929-1932
      - Calcium Wafers, 1930
      - Gastrogen, 1928-1930
  - Food Products
    - Baby Food
      - Gerber's, 1949-1951, (3 folders)
      - Gerber's, 1930-1948, (8 folders) (Box 75)
      - Heinz, 1935-1953, (17 folders)
      - Lacricin, 1929
      - Libby's, 1935-1940
      - Mellin's, 1932-1934
      - Nestle, 1923-1927, (2 folders)
      - Nestle, 1928-1934, (2 folders) (Box 76)
      - Robinson's Patent Barley, 1932
      - Similac, 1933-1934
      - S.M.A., 1931-1934, (2 folders)
      - Hygeia, 1931-1932
      - Lactogen, 1927
      - Mellin's, 1927-1931, (2 folders)
      - Mead's Dextro-Maltose, 1930-1932
      - Miscellaneous, 1942-1954, (13 folders)
      - Pablum, 1954
    - Baking Powder
      - Calumet, 1930-1942, (9 folders)
      - Calumet, 1923-1927, (5 folders) (Box 77)
      - Canadian Royal, 1924
      - Clabber Girl, 1934-1942, (2 folders)
      - Davis, 1923-1944, (3 folders)
      - Eggo, 1934
      - K.C., 1930-1934
      - Magic, 1927-1942, (4 folders)
  - Leather Goods, 1947-1949, (3 folders)
  - Welfare and Religious Organizations (Red Cross and others), 1954
  - Food Products
    - Bread
      - Mother Hubbard, 1930 (Box 78)
      - Oh Boy, 1934-1936
      - Peak Frean, 1929-1937, (2 folders)
      - Rice's, 1941
      - Ry-Krisp, 1930-1941, (12 folders)
      - Mrs. Schmidt's, 1927-1929, (2 folders)
      - Schrafft's, 1941-1942, (2 folders)
      - Schulze's, 1929
      - Silvercup, 1941-1953, (12 folders)
      - Southern Bread, 1928
      - Stone Baking Co., 1939
      - Taggart's, 1928
      - Taystee, 1930-1953, (11 folders)
      - Thomas, 1930-1952, (11 folders)
      - Thomas, 1944-1950, (8 folders) (Box 79)
      - Town Talk, 1942
      - Arnold, 1948-1949, (2 folders)
      - Bond, 1949
      - Van de Kamp's, 1930-1933, (2 folders)
      - Ward (Tip Top), 1922-1944, (13 folders)
      - Weber's, 1931-1933, (3 folders)
      - Wheat King, 1928-1929
      - White Rose, 1927-1928, (2 folders)
      - Wonder, 1929-1954, (19 folders) (Box 80)
      - Wonder, 1927-1932 (Box 81)
      - Miscellaneous, 1943-1953, (11 folders)
      - Miscellaneous, 1927-1942, (10 folders) (Box 82)
    - Bouillon Cubes and Meat Extracts, 1951
    - Butter and Butter Substitutes
      - Abbott's, 1932
      - Borden's, 1932
      - Cudahy's Delrich Margarine, 1947-1953, (7 folders)
      - Cedar Brook, 1928-1929
      - Durkee's Margarine, 1947-1953, (7 folders)
      - Durkee's Margarine, 1943-1946, (4 folders) (Box 83)
      - Jelke's Goodluck, 1929-1954, (11 folders)
      - Land O' Lakes, 1929-1954, (9 folders)
      - Meadow Gold, 1931-1937, (2 folders)
      - Morning Glory, 1928-1929
      - Nucoa Margarine, 1942-1954, (13 folders)
      - Nucoa Margarine, 1924-1941, (9 folders) (Box 84)
      - Parkay Margarine, 1948-1954, (7 folders)
      - Blue Valley, 1927-1932, (2 folders)
      - Jelke's Goodluck, 1920-1928, (2 folders)
      - Gem Nut, 1931
    - Candy
      - Miscellaneous, 1917-1943, (7 folders)
      - Miscellaneous, 1945-1948, (5 folders) (Box 85)
      - Mars, 1942
    - Canned Food
      - Borden's, 1943-1952, (9 folders)
      - Ann Page, 1939-1940, (2 folders)
      - Del Monte, 1936-1953, (15 folders)
      - Derby, 1941
      - Heinz, 1947-1953, (7 folders)
      - Miscellaneous, 1947
      - Heinz, 1939-1946, (7 folders) (Box 86)
      - Royal Scarlet, 1942-1951, (10 folders)
      - Van Camps, 1941
      - White Rose, 1943-1947, (5 folders)
      - Canapes (recipes), 1953-1956
      - Miscellaneous, 1944-1954, (10 folders)
      - Vegetables, 1943-1950, (3 folders)
      - Miscellaneous, 1941-1942, (2 folders)
    - Cereal
      - Armour's Oats, 1915-1925
      - Carnation Wheat, 1930-1932
      - Cheerioats, 1949-1952, (4 folders)
      - Cheerioats, 1941-1948, (8 folders) (Box 87)
      - Ralston, 1952
      - Cream of Wheat, 1940-1953, (13 folders)
      - Force, 1932-1934
      - Grape Nuts Flakes, 1945-1953, (7 folders)
    - Canned Food
      - Aylmer, 1935
      - Miscellaneous,, 1948-1953, (4 folders)
      - Miscellaneous, 1943-1947, (5 folders) (Box 88)
      - Bean Hole, 1927
      - Brown Beauty, 1919-1922
      - California Asparagus, 1926-1930
      - California Limas, 1928-1935
      - Campbell's Beans, 1922-1935, (3 folders)
      - Miscellaneous, 1946-1953, (13 folders)
      - Miscellaneous, 1949 (Box 89)
      - Corn, 1943-1951, (9 folders)
      - Clark's, 1932
      - Peas, 1943-1954, (12 folders)
      - Miscellaneous, 1938-1954, (8 folders)
      - Miscellaneous, 1927-1946, (7 folders) (Box 90)
    - Vegetables Fresh and Dried, 1930-1954, (14 folders)
    - Rice, 1921-1954, (13 folders)
    - Meat Spreads, 1946
    - Rice
      - Uncle Ben's Converted Rice, 1947-1952, (6 folders) (Box 91)
      - Comet, 1928-1941
      - River, 1935-1942, (2 folders)
      - Southern Rice Industry, 1936
      - Whitehouse, 1934
      - Miscellaneous, 1952-1953, (2 folders)
    - Sandwich Spreads, 1939
    - Chewing Gum
      - Miscellaneous, 1943
      - Adams, 1919-1940, (3 folders)
      - Beech-Nut, 1931-1947, (5 folders)
      - Beeman's, 1931-1934
      - Dentyne, 1917-1942, (3 folders)
      - Dentyne, 1935-1940 (Box 92)
      - Fleers, 1939
      - Teaberry, 1928-1929
      - Tempters, 1934-1935
      - Miscellaneous, 1947-1953, (2 folders)
      - Wrigley's, 1921-1954, (14 folders)
      - Wrigley's, 1945-1947, (3 folders) (Box 93)
      - Miscellaneous, 1944-1954, (9 folders)
  - Household Goods
    - Towels, 1950-1952, (3 folders)
    - Fabrics and Textile Processes--Sanforized, 1947-1954, (7 folders)
    - Cameras and Equipment
      - Ansco, 1949-1954, (2 folders)
      - Argus, 1949-1954, (2 folders)
      - Miscellaneous, 1949-1954, (4 folders)
  - Beverages
    - Coffee
      - Aborn's, 1944-1953, (8 folders) (Box 94)
      - Admiration, 1945-1947, (3 folders)
      - Airway, 1936-1953, (12 folders)
      - A&P, 1932-1953, (16 folders)
      - Astor, 1928-1934
      - A&P, 1931, 1950, 1953, (3 folders) (Box 95)
      - Astor, 1900s-1928
      - Atwood, 1934-1942, (2 folders)
      - Harrington Hall, 1909-1950, (7 folders)
      - Beech-Nut, 1917-1953, (19 folders)
      - Beech-Nut, 1929-1940, (2 folders) (Box 96)
      - Bevo, 1917-1920, n.d., (2 folders)
      - Blue Plate, (4 folders)
      - Borden's, 1920-1953, (10 folders)
      - Boscul, 1945-1949, (3 folders)
      - Breakstone, 1945
      - Butter Nut, 1922-1939, (4 folders)
      - Café du Monde, 1928
      - Café Rico, 1939-1940, (2 folders)
      - Camp, 1914-1928
      - Canova, 1930-1934, (2 folders)
      - Caswell's, 1928-1932
      - Chase & Sanborn, 1949-1953, (4 folders)
      - C.W. Brand, 1930
      - Del Monte, 1930-1948, (8 folders)
      - Don De, 1949-1950, (2 folders) (Box 97)
      - Nestle, 1924
      - A&P, 1940
      - Beech-Nut, 1947
      - Chase & Sanborn, 1954
      - Del Monte, 1932
  - Food Products
    - Crackers and Biscuits
      - Miscellaneous, 1917-1954, (12 folders)
      - Trix, 1939
      - Vegetized Wafers, 1929-1930
      - Miscellaneous, 1946-1949, (4 folders) (Box 98)
    - Cooking Oil
      - Mazola, 1928-1954, (11 folders)
      - Planter's HI-Hat, 1934-1936
      - Spry, 1936-1938
      - Wesson, 1945-1954, (9 folders)
      - Miscellaneous, 1943-1954, (10 folders)
      - Miscellaneous, 1952 (Box 99)
      - Wesson, 1947
    - Fish
      - Beardsley's, 1928-1931, (2 folders)
      - Birdseye, 1932
      - Burnham & Morrill Co., 1929-1931
      - Canned Salmon, 1936-1941, (3 folders)
      - Chatka, 1931-1938, (5 folders)
      - Chicken of the Sea, 1929-1941, (7 folders)
      - Davis, 1928-1929, (2 folders)
      - Del Monte, 1933-1940, (4 folders)
      - 40 Fathom Fish, 1928-1941, (2 folders)
      - Geisha, 1941
      - Gorton's, 1928-1954, (24 folders)
      - Icy Point, 1930
      - Japanese Deep Sea Crabmeat, 1930-1937, (5 folders)
      - Long Island Oysters, 1932
      - Namco, 1935-1937
      - Nordic, 1929
      - Pioneer, 1929 (Box 100)
      - Van Camps, 1935
      - Canned Miscellaneous, 1954
      - Frozen Miscellaneous, 1954
      - Miscellaneous, 1939-1953, (8 folders)
      - Canned Shrimp, 1941
    - Crackers
      - Beech-Nut, 1927-1940, (2 folders)
      - Colonial, 1930
      - Creamettes, 1933
      - Edgemont, 1925-1933
      - Educator, 1912-1933
      - Huntley & Palmers, 1925-1942, (2 folders)
      - Ivins, 1932
      - Johnston, 1934
      - McCormicks, 1919-1936
      - National Biscuit Co., 1949-1954, (6 folders)
      - National Biscuit Co., 1920-1948, (13 folders) (Box 101)
      - National Biscuit Co., 1953 (Box 102)
      - Ry-Krisp, 1942-1953, (11 folders)
      - Sawyer, 1932
      - Sunshine, 1922-1942, (9 folders)
      - Sun Wheat Biscuits, 1930
      - Sunshine, 1925-1953, (13 folders) (Box 103)
      - Wheatsworth, 1921-1930
      - Weston's, 1928-1930
      - Miscellaneous, 1945
    - Desserts
      - Gelatin, 1920-1944 (Box 104)
      - Pudding, 1920-1952, (15 folders)
      - Pie and Pie Filling
      - Miscellaneous, 1920-1956, (12 folders)
      - Good Luck, 1930
      - Pie Crust Maine Maid
      - Cream Whipping Aids, 1949-1954, (5 folders) (Box 105)
      - Cones, 1930
      - Ice Cream and Ice Cream Mixes
      - Breyer's, 1950
      - Sealtest, 1950
      - Miscellaneous, 1950
      - Chocolate
      - Miscellaneous, 1943-1954, (11 folders)
      - Baker's, 1942
      - Coconut, 1945-1954, (8 folders)
      - Flavoring Extracts
      - Miscellaneous, 1915-1954, (18 folders)
      - Chocolate, 1927
      - Desserts
      - Pies and Pie Fillings, 1954
      - Miscellaneous, 1948-1953, (5 folders) (Box 106)
    - Cream Whipping Aids, 1943-1948, (6 folders)
    - Dairy Products not covered by butter or milk
      - National Dairy Products Corp., 1943-1948, (6 folders)
      - Borden, 1945-1953, (8 folders)
      - Hood's, 1945
      - Miscellaneous, 1944-1954, (8 folders)
    - Eggs, 1928-1945, (5 folders)
    - Flavoring Extracts, 1949
    - Pies and Pie Fillings
      - Borden, 1942-1947, (4 folders)
    - Puddings and gelatin
      - Amazo, 1949-1954, (4 folders)
      - Argo, 1940
      - Gumperts Pudding, 1934-1935
      - Heinz Mince Meat and Puddings, 1935
      - Junket, 1943-1952, (7 folders)
      - Jell-O, 1943
      - Jell-O, 1925-1954, (17 folders) (Box 107)
      - Jell-O, 1951 (Box 108)
      - Junket, 1927-1951, (7 folders)
      - Knox Gelatin, 1939-1941
      - Kosto Pudding, 1930-1933
      - Kre-Mel, 1930-1942, (4 folders)
      - Kwik-Set, 1930
      - Minute Gelatin, 1894-1925
      - Minute Tapioca, 1925-1941, (4 folders)
      - Minute Tapioca, 1921-1942, (2 folders) (Box 109)
      - My-T-Fine, 1934-1954, (15 folders)
      - Plymouth Rock Gelatine, 1927-1930
      - Reichardt's Chocolate, 1928
      - Richardson and Robbins, 1921-1935
      - Rockwood's Decorettes, 1924-1926
      - Royal, 1941-1954, (14 folders)
      - Sparkle Gelatin, 1940
      - Junket, 1953
      - Jell-O, 1938-1941
      - Miscellaneous, 1953-1954, (2 folders)
    - Ice Cream and Ice Cream Mixes
      - Abbott's, 1952 (Box 110)
      - Abbottmaid, 1920-1926
      - Borden's, 1931-1940, (2 folders)
      - Breyer's, 1928-1954, (13 folders)
      - Dixies, 1937
      - Cardini, 1937
      - Chapman's, 1931-1932
      - Fro-Joy, 1928-1937, (2 folders)
      - Hood's, 1932
      - Horton's, 1918-1934, (4 folders)
      - Hydrox, 1923-1939, (4 folders) (Box 111)
      - Lipton Frostee Dessert Mix, 1951-1952, (2 folders)
      - Meadow Gold, 1931
      - Midco, 1938
      - Reid's, 1931-1941, (2 folders)
      - Reick's, 1928-1931
      - Sealtest, 1944-1954, (6 folders)
      - Smith Bros., 1933
      - Smoothie, 1933
      - Sunfreeze, 1933
      - Southern Dairies, 1927-1936, (2 folders)
      - Sunny Meadows, 1927
      - Supplee, 1932
      - Teall's, 1929
      - Tech, 1931
      - Velvet, 1930-1931
      - Cones, 1928-1929
      - Miscellaneous, 1949-1954
      - Miscellaneous, 1927-1951, (14 folders) (Box 112)
      - Breyer's, 1953
      - Sealtest, 1953
      - Lipton Frostee Dessert Mix, 1953
    - Flour
      - Pillsbury's Best, 1922-1937, (12 folders) (Box 113)
      - Pillsbury's Best Enriched, 1951-1954, (3 folders)
      - Pillsbury's Cake Flour, 1929-1936, (4 folders)
      - Pillsbury MinitMix, 1937
      - Pillsbury Pancake Mix, 1922-1939, (10 folders)
      - Pillsbury Semonlina, 1927-1930
      - Pillsbury Sno-Sheen, 1936
      - Pillsbury Wheat Bran, 1931
      - Presto, 1945
      - Red Band, 1933-1937, (2 folders)
      - Softasilk, 1952-1953, (2 folders)
  - Food Products
    - Flour
      - Pillsbury, 1945 (Box 114)
      - Presto, 1927-1948, (15 folders)
      - Sno Sheen cake flour, 1952
      - Softasilk, 1947-1951, (5 folders)
      - Jenny Wren, 1927-1929
      - Stoy soy flour, 1944
      - Suzanna pancake and waffle flour, 1944
      - Swan's Down, 1928-1949, (10 folders)
      - Pillsbury pie crust and cake mixes, 1949-1950, (2 folders)
      - Teco, 1927-1928 (Box 115)
      - Virginia Sweet, 1928
      - Pillsbury pie crust and cake mixes, 1952
      - Pillsbury hot roll and cake mixes, 1948
      - Swan's Down, 1929-1954, (6 folders)
      - Pillsbury, 1928-1951, (13 folders)
      - Miscellaneous, 1954
  - Beverages
    - Coffee
      - Savarin, 1953 (Box 116)
  - Food Products
    - Flour
      - Miscellaneous, 1948-1953, (6 folders)
      - Aunt Jemima, 1940-1954, (13 folders)
      - Cuplets, 1933-1939, (2 folders)
      - Ballard's, 1931-1937, (3 folders)
      - Ceresota, 1933
      - Betty Crocker, 1954
      - Ranch House pancake flour, 1944
      - Drifted Snow, 1942
      - Dromedary, 1944-1953, (10 folders)
      - Dromedary, 1936-1943, (6 folders) (Box 117)
      - Duff's, 1931-1953, (16 folders)
      - Flako, 1932-1953, (14 folders)
      - Flakorn, 1939-1940, (2 folders)
      - General Mills (Gold Medal, Bisquick), 1941-1945, (5 folders)
      - General Mills (Gold Medal, Bisquick), 1946-1954, (8 folders) (Box 118)
      - Betty Crocker, 1952-1953, (2 folders)
      - General Mills institutional, 1945-1948, (2 folders)
      - General Mills (Gold Medal, Softasilk), 1937-1952, (15 folders)
      - General Mills (Gold Medal, Bisquick), 1950-1954, (4 folders) (Box 119)
      - Gold Medal, 1920-1938, (16 folders)
      - Globe A1, 1942
      - Occident, 1929-1932, (2 folders)
      - Globe A1, 1930 (Box 120)
      - Golden Wheat Soy, 1944
      - Golden Soy Griddle, 1943-1944, (2 folders)
      - Hecker's, 1927-1942, (10 folders)
      - Hetty Harper's Brownie Mix, 1935
      - Jean's, 1937
      - Jenny Wren, 1931-1934, (2 folders)
      - Joy, 1927